import { useState, useRef, useEffect, useMemo } from 'react'
import './App.scss'

const soundEffect = (fileName: string) => {
    const sound = new Audio(`/sound-effects/${fileName}.wav`);
    sound.play();
}

const random = (min: number, max: number): number => {
    return Math.floor(Math.random() * (Math.floor(max) - Math.ceil(min) + 1)) + Math.ceil(min);
}

const randomFromList = (list: any[]): any => {
  return list[random(0, list.length - 1)]
}

const fisherYates = (list: any[]): any[] => {
  let limit = list.length - 1;
  while(limit > 0) {
        let position = random(0, limit);

        let tmp = list[position];
        list[position] = list[limit];
        list[limit] = tmp;

        limit--;
  }

  return list;
}

const removeAccents = (string: string): string => {
  if (!string) return ''

  return string.normalize("NFD").replace(/[\u0300-\u036f]/g, "");
}

const normalizeString = (string: string): string => {
  if (!string) return ''

  return removeAccents(string).toLowerCase().trim();
}

const levenshteinDistance = (a: string, b: string, corte = true): number => {
  if (!a || !b) return -1

  if (a.length === 0) return b.length;
  if (b.length === 0) return a.length;

  a = normalizeString(a);
  b = normalizeString(b);

  if (corte) {
     if (a.length > b.length) {
      let diferenca = a.length - b.length;
      a = a.slice(0, a.length - diferenca);
     } else if (a.length < b.length) {
      let diferenca = b.length - a.length;
      b = b.slice(0, b.length - diferenca);
     }
  }

  let matrix = [];

  for (let i = 0; i <= b.length; i++) {
      matrix[i] = [i];
  }

  for (let j = 0; j <= a.length; j++) {
      matrix[0][j] = j;
  }

  for (let i = 1; i <= b.length; i++) {
      for (let j = 1; j <= a.length; j++) {
         if (b.charAt(i - 1) == a.charAt(j - 1)) {
            matrix[i][j] = matrix[i - 1][j - 1];
         } else {
            matrix[i][j] = Math.min(matrix[i - 1][j - 1] + 1,
            Math.min(matrix[i][j - 1] + 1, matrix[i - 1][j] + 1));
         }
      }
  }

  return matrix[b.length][a.length];
}

const inList = (value: any, list: any[]): boolean => {
  for (let i = 0; i < list.length; i++) {
    if (value === list[i])
      return true
  }

  return false
}

const atLeastOneInList = (list1: any[], list2: any[]): boolean => {
  for (let i = 0; i < list1.length; i++) {
    for (let j = 0; j < list2.length; j++) {
      if (normalizeString(list1[i]) === normalizeString(list2[j])) {
        return true
      }
    }
  }

  return false
}

// atLeastOneInList(['Europa', 'Bandeira'], ['Mapa', 'Bandeira'])

const closestElement = (value: any, list: any[], ignore: any[] = []): any => {
  let closest = Number.POSITIVE_INFINITY
  let theOne
  for (let i = 0; i < list.length; i++) {
    if (!inList(list[i], ignore)) {
      let distance = levenshteinDistance(value, list[i])
      if (distance < closest) {
        closest = distance
        theOne = list[i]
      }
    }
  }

  return theOne
}

const getListFromObjectsAttr = (objects: any[], attr: string): any[] => {
  let list = []
  for (let i = 0; i < objects.length; i++) {
    list.push(objects[i][attr])
  }
  return list
}

const generateUniqueKey = () => {
  const alphabet = fisherYates(['a', 'b', 'c', 'd', 'e', 'f', 'g', 'h', 'i', 'j', 'k', 'l', 'm', 'n', 'o', 'p', 'q', 'r', 's', 't', 'u', 'v', 'w', 'x', 'y', 'z', 'A', 'B', 'C', 'D', 'E', 'F', 'G', 'H', 'I', 'J', 'K', 'L', 'M', 'N', 'O', 'P', 'Q', 'R', 'S', 'T', 'U', 'V', 'W', 'X', 'Y', 'Z', '0', '1', '2', '3', '4', '5', '6', '7', '8', '9', '!', '@', '#', '$', '%', '&', '*', '-', '_', '+', '='])
  const date = new Date()
  let key = `${date.getTime()}`
  for (let i = 0; i < 12; i++) {
    key += randomFromList(alphabet)
  }

  return key
}

const copy = (element: any): any => {
  return JSON.parse(JSON.stringify(element))
}

let ds = [{"id":0,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":3,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":4,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":5,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":6,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":7,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":8,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":9,"question":"songs/01 A Hard Day's Night_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"A Hard Day's Night","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":10,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":11,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":12,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":13,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":14,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":15,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":16,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":17,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":18,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":19,"question":"songs/02 I Should Have Known Better_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"I Should Have Known Better","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":20,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":21,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":22,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":23,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":24,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":25,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":26,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":27,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":28,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":29,"question":"songs/03 If I Fell_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"If I Fell","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":30,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":31,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":32,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":33,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":34,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":35,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":36,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":37,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":38,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":39,"question":"songs/04 I'm Happy Just To Dance With You_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"I'm Happy Just To Dance With You","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":40,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":41,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":42,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":43,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":44,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":45,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":46,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":47,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":48,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":49,"question":"songs/05 And I Love Her_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"And I Love Her","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":50,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":51,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":52,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":53,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":54,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":55,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":56,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":57,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":58,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":59,"question":"songs/06 Tell Me Why_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"Tell Me Why","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":60,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":61,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":62,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":63,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":64,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":65,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":66,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":67,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":68,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":69,"question":"songs/07 Can't Buy Me Love_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"Can't Buy Me Love","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":70,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":71,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":72,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":73,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":74,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":75,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":76,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":77,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":78,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":79,"question":"songs/08 Any Time At All_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"Any Time At All","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":80,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":81,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":82,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":83,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":84,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":85,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":86,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":87,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":88,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":89,"question":"songs/09 I'll Cry Instead_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"I'll Cry Instead","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":90,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":91,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":92,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":93,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":94,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":95,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":96,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":97,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":98,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":99,"question":"songs/10 Things We Said Today_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"Things We Said Today","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":100,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":101,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":102,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":103,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":104,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":105,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":106,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":107,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":108,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":109,"question":"songs/11 When I Get Home_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"When I Get Home","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":110,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":111,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":112,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":113,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":114,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":115,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":116,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":117,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":118,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":119,"question":"songs/12 You Can't Do That_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"You Can't Do That","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":120,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_1.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":121,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_2.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":122,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_3.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":123,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_4.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":124,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_5.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":125,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_6.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":126,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_7.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":127,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_8.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":128,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_9.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":129,"question":"songs/13 I'll Be Back_A Hard Day's Night_10.mp3","answer":"I'll Be Back","categories":["A Hard Day's Night"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":130,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":131,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":132,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":133,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":134,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":135,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":136,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":137,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":138,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":139,"question":"songs/01 Come Together_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Come Together","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":140,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":141,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":142,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":143,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":144,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":145,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":146,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":147,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":148,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":149,"question":"songs/02 Something_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Something","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":150,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":151,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":152,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":153,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":154,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":155,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":156,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":157,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":158,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":159,"question":"songs/03 Maxwell's Silver Hammer_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Maxwell's Silver Hammer","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":160,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":161,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":162,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":163,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":164,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":165,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":166,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":167,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":168,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":169,"question":"songs/04 Oh! Darling_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Oh! Darling","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":170,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":171,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":172,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":173,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":174,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":175,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":176,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":177,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":178,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":179,"question":"songs/05 Octopus's Garden_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Octopus's Garden","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":180,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":181,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":182,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":183,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":184,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":185,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":186,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":187,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":188,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":189,"question":"songs/06 I Want You (She's So Heavy)_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"I Want You (She's So Heavy)","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":190,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":191,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":192,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":193,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":194,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":195,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":196,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":197,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":198,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":199,"question":"songs/07 Here Comes The Sun_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Here Comes The Sun","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":200,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":201,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":202,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":203,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":204,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":205,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":206,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":207,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":208,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":209,"question":"songs/08 Because_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Because","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":210,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":211,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":212,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":213,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":214,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":215,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":216,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":217,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":218,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":219,"question":"songs/09 You Never Give Me Your Money_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"You Never Give Me Your Money","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":220,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":221,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":222,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":223,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":224,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":225,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":226,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":227,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":228,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":229,"question":"songs/10 Sun King_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Sun King","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":230,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":231,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":232,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":233,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":234,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":235,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":236,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":237,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":238,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":239,"question":"songs/11 Mean Mr. Mustard_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Mean Mr. Mustard","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":240,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":241,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":242,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":243,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":244,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":245,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":246,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":247,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":248,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":249,"question":"songs/12 Polythene Pam_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Polythene Pam","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":250,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":251,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":252,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":253,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":254,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":255,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":256,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":257,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":258,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":259,"question":"songs/13 She Came In Through The Bathroom Window_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"She Came In Through The Bathroom Window","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":260,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":261,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":262,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":263,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":264,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":265,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":266,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":267,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":268,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":269,"question":"songs/14 Golden Slumbers_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Golden Slumbers","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":270,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":271,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":272,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":273,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":274,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":275,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":276,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":277,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":278,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":279,"question":"songs/15 Carry That Weight_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"Carry That Weight","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":280,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":281,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":282,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":283,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":284,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":285,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":286,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":287,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":288,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":289,"question":"songs/16 The End_Abbey Road_10.mp3","answer":"The End","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":290,"question":"songs/17 Her Majesty_Abbey Road_1.mp3","answer":"Her Majesty","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":291,"question":"songs/17 Her Majesty_Abbey Road_2.mp3","answer":"Her Majesty","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":292,"question":"songs/17 Her Majesty_Abbey Road_3.mp3","answer":"Her Majesty","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":293,"question":"songs/17 Her Majesty_Abbey Road_4.mp3","answer":"Her Majesty","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":294,"question":"songs/17 Her Majesty_Abbey Road_5.mp3","answer":"Her Majesty","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":295,"question":"songs/17 Her Majesty_Abbey Road_6.mp3","answer":"Her Majesty","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":296,"question":"songs/17 Her Majesty_Abbey Road_7.mp3","answer":"Her Majesty","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":297,"question":"songs/17 Her Majesty_Abbey Road_8.mp3","answer":"Her Majesty","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":298,"question":"songs/17 Her Majesty_Abbey Road_9.mp3","answer":"Her Majesty","categories":["Abbey Road"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":300,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":301,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":302,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":303,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":304,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":305,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":306,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":307,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":308,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":309,"question":"songs/01 No Reply_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"No Reply","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":310,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":311,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":312,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":313,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":314,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":315,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":316,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":317,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":318,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":319,"question":"songs/02 I'm A Loser_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"I'm A Loser","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":320,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":321,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":322,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":323,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":324,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":325,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":326,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":327,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":328,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":329,"question":"songs/03 Baby's In Black_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"Baby's In Black","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":330,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":331,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":332,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":333,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":334,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":335,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":336,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":337,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":338,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":339,"question":"songs/04 Rock And Roll Music_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"Rock And Roll Music","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":340,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":341,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":342,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":343,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":344,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":345,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":346,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":347,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":348,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":349,"question":"songs/05 I'll Follow The Sun_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"I'll Follow The Sun","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":350,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":351,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":352,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":353,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":354,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":355,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":356,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":357,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":358,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":359,"question":"songs/06 Mr. Moonlight_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"Mr. Moonlight","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":360,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":361,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":362,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":363,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":364,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":365,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":366,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":367,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":368,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":369,"question":"songs/07 Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"Kansas City - Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":370,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":371,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":372,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":373,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":374,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":375,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":376,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":377,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":378,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":379,"question":"songs/08 Eight Days A Week_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"Eight Days A Week","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":380,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":381,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":382,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":383,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":384,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":385,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":386,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":387,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":388,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":389,"question":"songs/09 Words Of Love_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"Words Of Love","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":390,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":391,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":392,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":393,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":394,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":395,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":396,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":397,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":398,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":399,"question":"songs/10 Honey Don't_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"Honey Don't","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":400,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":401,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":402,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":403,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":404,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":405,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":406,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":407,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":408,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":409,"question":"songs/11 Every Little Thing_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"Every Little Thing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":410,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":411,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":412,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":413,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":414,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":415,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":416,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":417,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":418,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":419,"question":"songs/12 I Don't Want To Spoil The Party_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"I Don't Want To Spoil The Party","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":420,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":421,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":422,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":423,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":424,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":425,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":426,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":427,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":428,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":429,"question":"songs/13 What You're Doing_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"What You're Doing","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":430,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_1.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":431,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_2.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":432,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_3.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":433,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_4.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":434,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_5.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":435,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_6.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":436,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_7.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":437,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_8.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":438,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_9.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":439,"question":"songs/14 Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby_Beatles For Sale_10.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Trying To Be My Baby","categories":["Beatles For Sale"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":440,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":441,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":442,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":443,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":444,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":445,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":446,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":447,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":448,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":449,"question":"songs/01 Help!_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"Help!","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":450,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":451,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":452,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":453,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":454,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":455,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":456,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":457,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":458,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":459,"question":"songs/02 The Night Before_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"The Night Before","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":460,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":461,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":462,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":463,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":464,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":465,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":466,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":467,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":468,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":469,"question":"songs/03 You've Got To Hide Your Love Away_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"You've Got To Hide Your Love Away","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":470,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":471,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":472,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":473,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":474,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":475,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":476,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":477,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":478,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":479,"question":"songs/04 I Need You_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"I Need You","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":480,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":481,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":482,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":483,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":484,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":485,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":486,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":487,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":488,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":489,"question":"songs/05 Another Girl_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"Another Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":490,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":491,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":492,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":493,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":494,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":495,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":496,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":497,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":498,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":499,"question":"songs/06 You're Going To Lose That Girl_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"You're Going To Lose That Girl","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":500,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":501,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":502,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":503,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":504,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":505,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":506,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":507,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":508,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":509,"question":"songs/07 Ticket To Ride_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"Ticket To Ride","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":510,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":511,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":512,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":513,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":514,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":515,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":516,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":517,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":518,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":519,"question":"songs/08 Act Naturally_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"Act Naturally","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":520,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":521,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":522,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":523,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":524,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":525,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":526,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":527,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":528,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":529,"question":"songs/09 It's Only Love_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"It's Only Love","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":530,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":531,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":532,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":533,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":534,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":535,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":536,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":537,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":538,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":539,"question":"songs/10 You Like Me Too Much_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"You Like Me Too Much","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":540,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":541,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":542,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":543,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":544,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":545,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":546,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":547,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":548,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":549,"question":"songs/11 Tell Me What You See_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"Tell Me What You See","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":550,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":551,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":552,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":553,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":554,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":555,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":556,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":557,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":558,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":559,"question":"songs/12 I`ve Just Seen A Face_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"I`ve Just Seen A Face","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":560,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":561,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":562,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":563,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":564,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":565,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":566,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":567,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":568,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":569,"question":"songs/13 Yesterday_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"Yesterday","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":570,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_1.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":571,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_2.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":572,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_3.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":573,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_4.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":574,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_5.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":575,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_6.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":576,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_7.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":577,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_8.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":578,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_9.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":579,"question":"songs/14 Dizzy Miss Lizzy_Help!_10.mp3","answer":"Dizzy Miss Lizzy","categories":["Help!"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":580,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":581,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":582,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":583,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":584,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":585,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":586,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":587,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":588,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":589,"question":"songs/01 Two Of Us_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"Two Of Us","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":590,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":591,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":592,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":593,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":594,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":595,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":596,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":597,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":598,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":599,"question":"songs/02 Dig A Pony_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"Dig A Pony","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":600,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":601,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":602,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":603,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":604,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":605,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":606,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":607,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":608,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":609,"question":"songs/03 Across The Universe_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":610,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":611,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":612,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":613,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":614,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":615,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":616,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":617,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":618,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":619,"question":"songs/04 I Me Mine_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"I Me Mine","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":620,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":621,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":622,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":623,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":624,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":625,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":626,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":627,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":628,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":629,"question":"songs/05 Dig It_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"Dig It","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":630,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":631,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":632,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":633,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":634,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":635,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":636,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":637,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":638,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":639,"question":"songs/06 Let It Be_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":640,"question":"songs/07 Maggie Mae_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"Maggie Mae","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":641,"question":"songs/07 Maggie Mae_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"Maggie Mae","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":642,"question":"songs/07 Maggie Mae_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"Maggie Mae","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":643,"question":"songs/07 Maggie Mae_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"Maggie Mae","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":644,"question":"songs/07 Maggie Mae_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"Maggie Mae","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":645,"question":"songs/07 Maggie Mae_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"Maggie Mae","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":646,"question":"songs/07 Maggie Mae_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"Maggie Mae","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":647,"question":"songs/07 Maggie Mae_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"Maggie Mae","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":648,"question":"songs/07 Maggie Mae_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"Maggie Mae","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":650,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":651,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":652,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":653,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":654,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":655,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":656,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":657,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":658,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":659,"question":"songs/08 I've Got A Feeling_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"I've Got A Feeling","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":660,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":661,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":662,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":663,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":664,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":665,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":666,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":667,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":668,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":669,"question":"songs/09 One After 909_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"One After 909","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":670,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":671,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":672,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":673,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":674,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":675,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":676,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":677,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":678,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":679,"question":"songs/10 The Long And Winding Road_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"The Long And Winding Road","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":680,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":681,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":682,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":683,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":684,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":685,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":686,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":687,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":688,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":689,"question":"songs/11 For You Blue_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"For You Blue","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":690,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_1.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":691,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_2.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":692,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_3.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":693,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_4.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":694,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_5.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":695,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_6.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":696,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_7.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":697,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_8.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":698,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_9.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":699,"question":"songs/12 Get Back_Let It Be_10.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Let It Be"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":700,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":701,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":702,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":703,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":704,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":705,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":706,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":707,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":708,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":709,"question":"songs/01 Magical Mystery Tour_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"Magical Mystery Tour","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":710,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":711,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":712,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":713,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":714,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":715,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":716,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":717,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":718,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":719,"question":"songs/02 The Fool On The Hill_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"The Fool On The Hill","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":720,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":721,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":722,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":723,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":724,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":725,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":726,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":727,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":728,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":729,"question":"songs/03 Flying_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"Flying","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":730,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":731,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":732,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":733,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":734,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":735,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":736,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":737,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":738,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":739,"question":"songs/04 Blue Jay Way_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"Blue Jay Way","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":740,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":741,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":742,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":743,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":744,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":745,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":746,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":747,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":748,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":749,"question":"songs/05 Your Mother Should Know_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"Your Mother Should Know","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":750,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":751,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":752,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":753,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":754,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":755,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":756,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":757,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":758,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":759,"question":"songs/06 I Am The Walrus_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"I Am The Walrus","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":760,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":761,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":762,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":763,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":764,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":765,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":766,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":767,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":768,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":769,"question":"songs/07 Hello Goodbye_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"Hello Goodbye","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":770,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":771,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":772,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":773,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":774,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":775,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":776,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":777,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":778,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":779,"question":"songs/08 Strawberry Fields Forever_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"Strawberry Fields Forever","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":780,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":781,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":782,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":783,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":784,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":785,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":786,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":787,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":788,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":789,"question":"songs/09 Penny Lane_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"Penny Lane","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":790,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":791,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":792,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":793,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":794,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":795,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":796,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":797,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":798,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":799,"question":"songs/10 Baby You're A Rich Man_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"Baby You're A Rich Man","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":800,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_1.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":801,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_2.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":802,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_3.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":803,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_4.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":804,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_5.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":805,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_6.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":806,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_7.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":807,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_8.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":808,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_9.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":809,"question":"songs/11 All You Need Is Love_Magical Mystery Tour_10.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Magical Mystery Tour"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":810,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":811,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":812,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":813,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":814,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":815,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":816,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":817,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":818,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":819,"question":"songs/01 I Saw Her Standing There_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"I Saw Her Standing There","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":820,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":821,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":822,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":823,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":824,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":825,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":826,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":827,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":828,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":829,"question":"songs/02 Misery_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Misery","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":830,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":831,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":832,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":833,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":834,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":835,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":836,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":837,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":838,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":839,"question":"songs/03 Anna (Go To Him)_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Anna (Go To Him)","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":840,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":841,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":842,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":843,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":844,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":845,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":846,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":847,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":848,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":849,"question":"songs/04 Chains_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Chains","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":850,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":851,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":852,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":853,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":854,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":855,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":856,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":857,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":858,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":859,"question":"songs/05 Boys_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Boys","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":860,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":861,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":862,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":863,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":864,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":865,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":866,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":867,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":868,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":869,"question":"songs/06 Ask Me Why_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Ask Me Why","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":870,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":871,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":872,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":873,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":874,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":875,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":876,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":877,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":878,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":879,"question":"songs/07 Please Please Me_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Please Please Me","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":880,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":881,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":882,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":883,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":884,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":885,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":886,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":887,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":888,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":889,"question":"songs/08 Love Me Do_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":890,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":891,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":892,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":893,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":894,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":895,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":896,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":897,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":898,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":899,"question":"songs/09 P.S. I Love You_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"P.S. I Love You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":900,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":901,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":902,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":903,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":904,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":905,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":906,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":907,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":908,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":909,"question":"songs/10 Baby It's You_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Baby It's You","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":910,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":911,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":912,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":913,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":914,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":915,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":916,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":917,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":918,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":919,"question":"songs/11 Do You Want To Know A Secret_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Do You Want To Know A Secret","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":920,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":921,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":922,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":923,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":924,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":925,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":926,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":927,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":928,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":929,"question":"songs/12 A Taste Of Honey_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"A Taste Of Honey","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":930,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":931,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":932,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":933,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":934,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":935,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":936,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":937,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":938,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":939,"question":"songs/13 There's A Place_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"There's A Place","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":940,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_1.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":941,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_2.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":942,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_3.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":943,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_4.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":944,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_5.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":945,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_6.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":946,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_7.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":947,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_8.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":948,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_9.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":949,"question":"songs/14 Twist And Shout_Please Please Me_10.mp3","answer":"Twist And Shout","categories":["Please Please Me"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":950,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":951,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":952,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":953,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":954,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":955,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":956,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":957,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":958,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":959,"question":"songs/01 Taxman_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"Taxman","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":960,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":961,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":962,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":963,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":964,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":965,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":966,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":967,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":968,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":969,"question":"songs/02 Eleanor Rigby_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"Eleanor Rigby","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":970,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":971,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":972,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":973,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":974,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":975,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":976,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":977,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":978,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":979,"question":"songs/03 I'm Only Sleeping_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"I'm Only Sleeping","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":980,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":981,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":982,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":983,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":984,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":985,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":986,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":987,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":988,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":989,"question":"songs/04 Love You To_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"Love You To","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":990,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":991,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":992,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":993,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":994,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":995,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":996,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":997,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":998,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":999,"question":"songs/05 Here, There And Everywhere_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"Here, There And Everywhere","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1000,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1001,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1002,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1003,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1004,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1005,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1006,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1007,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1008,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1009,"question":"songs/06 Yellow Submarine_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1010,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1011,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1012,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1013,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1014,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1015,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1016,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1017,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1018,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1019,"question":"songs/07 She Said She Said_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"She Said She Said","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1020,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1021,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1022,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1023,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1024,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1025,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1026,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1027,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1028,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1029,"question":"songs/08 Good Day Sunshine_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"Good Day Sunshine","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1030,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1031,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1032,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1033,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1034,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1035,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1036,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1037,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1038,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1039,"question":"songs/09 And Your Bird Can Sing_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"And Your Bird Can Sing","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1040,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1041,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1042,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1043,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1044,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1045,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1046,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1047,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1048,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1049,"question":"songs/10 For No One_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"For No One","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1050,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1051,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1052,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1053,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1054,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1055,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1056,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1057,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1058,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1059,"question":"songs/11 Doctor Robert_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"Doctor Robert","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1060,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1061,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1062,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1063,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1064,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1065,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1066,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1067,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1068,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1069,"question":"songs/12 I Want To Tell You_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"I Want To Tell You","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1070,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1071,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1072,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1073,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1074,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1075,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1076,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1077,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1078,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1079,"question":"songs/13 Got To Get You Into My Life_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"Got To Get You Into My Life","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1080,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_1.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1081,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_2.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1082,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_3.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1083,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_4.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1084,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_5.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1085,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_6.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1086,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_7.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1087,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_8.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1088,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_9.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1089,"question":"songs/14 Tomorrow Never Knows_Revolver_10.mp3","answer":"Tomorrow Never Knows","categories":["Revolver"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1090,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1091,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1092,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1093,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1094,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1095,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1096,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1097,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1098,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1099,"question":"songs/01 Drive My Car_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"Drive My Car","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1100,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1101,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1102,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1103,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1104,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1105,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1106,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1107,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1108,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1109,"question":"songs/02 Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"Norwegian Wood (The Bird Has Flown)","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1110,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1111,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1112,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1113,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1114,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1115,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1116,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1117,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1118,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1119,"question":"songs/03 You Won't See Me_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"You Won't See Me","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1120,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1121,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1122,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1123,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1124,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1125,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1126,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1127,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1128,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1129,"question":"songs/04 Nowhere Man_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"Nowhere Man","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1130,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1131,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1132,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1133,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1134,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1135,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1136,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1137,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1138,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1139,"question":"songs/05 Think For Yourself_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"Think For Yourself","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1140,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1141,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1142,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1143,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1144,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1145,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1146,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1147,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1148,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1149,"question":"songs/06 The Word_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"The Word","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1150,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1151,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1152,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1153,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1154,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1155,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1156,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1157,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1158,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1159,"question":"songs/07 Michelle_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"Michelle","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1160,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1161,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1162,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1163,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1164,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1165,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1166,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1167,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1168,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1169,"question":"songs/08 What Goes On_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"What Goes On","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1170,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1171,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1172,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1173,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1174,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1175,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1176,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1177,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1178,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1179,"question":"songs/09 Girl_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"Girl","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1180,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1181,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1182,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1183,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1184,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1185,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1186,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1187,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1188,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1189,"question":"songs/10 I'm Looking Through You_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"I'm Looking Through You","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1190,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1191,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1192,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1193,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1194,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1195,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1196,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1197,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1198,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1199,"question":"songs/11 In My Life_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"In My Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1200,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1201,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1202,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1203,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1204,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1205,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1206,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1207,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1208,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1209,"question":"songs/12 Wait_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"Wait","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1210,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1211,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1212,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1213,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1214,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1215,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1216,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1217,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1218,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1219,"question":"songs/13 If I Needed Someone_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"If I Needed Someone","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1220,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_1.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1221,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_2.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1222,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_3.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1223,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_4.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1224,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_5.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1225,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_6.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1226,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_7.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1227,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_8.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1228,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_9.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1229,"question":"songs/14 Run For Your Life_Rubber Soul_10.mp3","answer":"Run For Your Life","categories":["Rubber Soul"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1230,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1231,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1232,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1233,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1234,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1235,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1236,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1237,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1238,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1239,"question":"songs/01 Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1240,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1241,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1242,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1243,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1244,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1245,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1246,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1247,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1248,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1249,"question":"songs/02 With A Little Help From My Friends_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"With A Little Help From My Friends","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1250,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1251,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1252,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1253,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1254,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1255,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1256,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1257,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1258,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1259,"question":"songs/03 Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1260,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1261,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1262,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1263,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1264,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1265,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1266,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1267,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1268,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1269,"question":"songs/04 Getting Better_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"Getting Better","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1270,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1271,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1272,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1273,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1274,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1275,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1276,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1277,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1278,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1279,"question":"songs/05 Fixing A Hole_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"Fixing A Hole","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1280,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1281,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1282,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1283,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1284,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1285,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1286,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1287,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1288,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1289,"question":"songs/06 She's Leaving Home_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"She's Leaving Home","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1290,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1291,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1292,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1293,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1294,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1295,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1296,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1297,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1298,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1299,"question":"songs/07 Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"Being For The Benefit Of Mr Kite","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1300,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1301,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1302,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1303,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1304,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1305,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1306,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1307,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1308,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1309,"question":"songs/08 Within You Without You_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"Within You Without You","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1310,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1311,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1312,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1313,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1314,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1315,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1316,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1317,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1318,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1319,"question":"songs/09 When I'm Sixty-Four_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"When I'm Sixty-Four","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1320,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1321,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1322,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1323,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1324,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1325,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1326,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1327,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1328,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1329,"question":"songs/10 Lovely Rita_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"Lovely Rita","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1330,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1331,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1332,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1333,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1334,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1335,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1336,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1337,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1338,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1339,"question":"songs/11 Good Morning Good Morning_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"Good Morning Good Morning","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1340,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1341,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1342,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1343,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1344,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1345,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1346,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1347,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1348,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1349,"question":"songs/12 Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"Sgt Peppers..(Reprise)","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1350,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_1.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1351,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_2.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1352,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_3.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1353,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_4.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1354,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_5.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1355,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_6.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1356,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_7.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1357,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_8.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1358,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_9.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1359,"question":"songs/13 A Day In The Life_Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band_10.mp3","answer":"A Day In The Life","categories":["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1360,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1361,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1362,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1363,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1364,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1365,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1366,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1367,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1368,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1369,"question":"songs/01 Back In The U.S.S.R._The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Back In The U.S.S.R.","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1370,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1371,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1372,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1373,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1374,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1375,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1376,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1377,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1378,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1379,"question":"songs/02 Dear Prudence_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Dear Prudence","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1380,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1381,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1382,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1383,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1384,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1385,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1386,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1387,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1388,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1389,"question":"songs/03 Glass Onion_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Glass Onion","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1390,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1391,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1392,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1393,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1394,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1395,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1396,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1397,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1398,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1399,"question":"songs/04 Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1400,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1401,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1402,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1403,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1404,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1405,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1406,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1407,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1408,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1409,"question":"songs/05 Wild Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Wild Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1410,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1411,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1412,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1413,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1414,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1415,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1416,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1417,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1418,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1419,"question":"songs/06 The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"The Continuing Story Of Bungalow Bill","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1420,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1421,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1422,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1423,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1424,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1425,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1426,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1427,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1428,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1429,"question":"songs/07 While My Guitar Gently Weeps_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"While My Guitar Gently Weeps","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1430,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1431,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1432,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1433,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1434,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1435,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1436,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1437,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1438,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1439,"question":"songs/08 Happiness Is A Warm Gun_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Happiness Is A Warm Gun","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1440,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1441,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1442,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1443,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1444,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1445,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1446,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1447,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1448,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1449,"question":"songs/09 Martha My Dear_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Martha My Dear","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1450,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1451,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1452,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1453,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1454,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1455,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1456,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1457,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1458,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1459,"question":"songs/10 I'm So Tired_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"I'm So Tired","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1460,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1461,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1462,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1463,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1464,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1465,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1466,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1467,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1468,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1469,"question":"songs/11 Blackbird_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Blackbird","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1470,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1471,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1472,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1473,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1474,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1475,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1476,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1477,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1478,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1479,"question":"songs/12 Piggies_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Piggies","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1480,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1481,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1482,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1483,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1484,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1485,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1486,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1487,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1488,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1489,"question":"songs/13 Rocky Raccoon_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Rocky Raccoon","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1490,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1491,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1492,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1493,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1494,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1495,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1496,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1497,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1498,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1499,"question":"songs/14 Don't Pass Me By_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Don't Pass Me By","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1500,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1501,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1502,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1503,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1504,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1505,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1506,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1507,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1508,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1509,"question":"songs/15 Why Don't We Do It In The Road_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Why Don't We Do It In The Road","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1510,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1511,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1512,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1513,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1514,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1515,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1516,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1517,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1518,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1519,"question":"songs/16 I Will_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"I Will","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1520,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_1.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1521,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_2.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1522,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_3.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1523,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_4.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1524,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_5.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1525,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_6.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1526,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_7.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1527,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_8.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1528,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_9.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1529,"question":"songs/17 Julia_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]_10.mp3","answer":"Julia","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1530,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1531,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1532,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1533,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1534,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1535,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1536,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1537,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1538,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1539,"question":"songs/01 Birthday_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Birthday","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1540,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1541,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1542,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1543,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1544,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1545,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1546,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1547,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1548,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1549,"question":"songs/02 Yer Blues_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Yer Blues","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1550,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1551,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1552,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1553,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1554,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1555,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1556,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1557,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1558,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1559,"question":"songs/03 Mother Nature's Son_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Mother Nature's Son","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1560,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1561,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1562,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1563,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1564,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1565,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1566,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1567,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1568,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1569,"question":"songs/04 Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Everybody's Got Something To Hide Except Me And My Monkey","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1570,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1571,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1572,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1573,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1574,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1575,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1576,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1577,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1578,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1579,"question":"songs/05 Sexy Sadie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Sexy Sadie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1580,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1581,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1582,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1583,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1584,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1585,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1586,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1587,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1588,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1589,"question":"songs/06 Helter Skelter_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Helter Skelter","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1590,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1591,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1592,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1593,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1594,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1595,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1596,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1597,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1598,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1599,"question":"songs/07 Long, Long, Long_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Long, Long, Long","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1600,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1601,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1602,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1603,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1604,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1605,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1606,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1607,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1608,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1609,"question":"songs/08 Revolution 1_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Revolution 1","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1610,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1611,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1612,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1613,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1614,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1615,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1616,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1617,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1618,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1619,"question":"songs/09 Honey Pie_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Honey Pie","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1620,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1621,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1622,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1623,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1624,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1625,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1626,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1627,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1628,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1629,"question":"songs/10 Savoy Truffle_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Savoy Truffle","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1630,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1631,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1632,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1633,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1634,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1635,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1636,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1637,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1638,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1639,"question":"songs/11 Cry Baby Cry_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Cry Baby Cry","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1640,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1641,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1642,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1643,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1644,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1645,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1646,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1647,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1648,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1649,"question":"songs/12 Revolution 9_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Revolution 9","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1650,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_1.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1651,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_2.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1652,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_3.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1653,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_4.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1654,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_5.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1655,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_6.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1656,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_7.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1657,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_8.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1658,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_9.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1659,"question":"songs/13 Good Night_The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]_10.mp3","answer":"Good Night","categories":["The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1660,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1661,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1662,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1663,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1664,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1665,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1666,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1667,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1668,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1669,"question":"songs/01 It Won't Be Long_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"It Won't Be Long","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1670,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1671,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1672,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1673,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1674,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1675,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1676,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1677,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1678,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1679,"question":"songs/02 All I've Got To Do_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"All I've Got To Do","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1680,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1681,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1682,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1683,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1684,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1685,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1686,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1687,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1688,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1689,"question":"songs/03 All My Loving_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"All My Loving","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1690,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1691,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1692,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1693,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1694,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1695,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1696,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1697,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1698,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1699,"question":"songs/04 Don't Bother Me_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"Don't Bother Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1700,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1701,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1702,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1703,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1704,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1705,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1706,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1707,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1708,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1709,"question":"songs/05 Little Child_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"Little Child","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1710,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1711,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1712,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1713,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1714,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1715,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1716,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1717,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1718,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1719,"question":"songs/06 Till There Was You_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"Till There Was You","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1720,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1721,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1722,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1723,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1724,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1725,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1726,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1727,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1728,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1729,"question":"songs/07 Please Mister Postman_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"Please Mister Postman","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1730,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1731,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1732,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1733,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1734,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1735,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1736,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1737,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1738,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1739,"question":"songs/08 Roll Over Beethoven_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"Roll Over Beethoven","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1740,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1741,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1742,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1743,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1744,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1745,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1746,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1747,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1748,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1749,"question":"songs/09 Hold Me Tight_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"Hold Me Tight","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1750,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1751,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1752,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1753,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1754,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1755,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1756,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1757,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1758,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1759,"question":"songs/10 You Really Got A Hold On Me_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"You Really Got A Hold On Me","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1760,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1761,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1762,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1763,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1764,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1765,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1766,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1767,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1768,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1769,"question":"songs/11 I Wanna Be Your Man_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"I Wanna Be Your Man","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1770,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1771,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1772,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1773,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1774,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1775,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1776,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1777,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1778,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1779,"question":"songs/12 Devil In Her Heart_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"Devil In Her Heart","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1780,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1781,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1782,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1783,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1784,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1785,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1786,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1787,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1788,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1789,"question":"songs/13 Not A Second Time_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"Not A Second Time","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1790,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_1.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1791,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_2.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1792,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_3.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1793,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_4.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1794,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_5.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1795,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_6.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1796,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_7.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1797,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_8.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1798,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_9.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1799,"question":"songs/14 Money (That's What I Want)_With The Beatles_10.mp3","answer":"Money (That's What I Want)","categories":["With The Beatles"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1800,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1801,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1802,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1803,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1804,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1805,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1806,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1807,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1808,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1809,"question":"songs/01 Yellow Submarine_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1810,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1811,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1812,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1813,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1814,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1815,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1816,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1817,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1818,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1819,"question":"songs/02 Only A Northern Song_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"Only A Northern Song","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1820,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1821,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1822,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1823,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1824,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1825,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1826,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1827,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1828,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1829,"question":"songs/03 All Together Now_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"All Together Now","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1830,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1831,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1832,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1833,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1834,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1835,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1836,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1837,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1838,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1839,"question":"songs/04 Hey Bulldog_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"Hey Bulldog","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1840,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1841,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1842,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1843,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1844,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1845,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1846,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1847,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1848,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1849,"question":"songs/05 It's All Too Much_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"It's All Too Much","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1850,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1851,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1852,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1853,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1854,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1855,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1856,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1857,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1858,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1859,"question":"songs/06 All You Need Is Love_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"All You Need Is Love","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1860,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1861,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1862,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1863,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1864,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1865,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1866,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1867,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1868,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1869,"question":"songs/07 Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1870,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1871,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1872,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1873,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1874,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1875,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1876,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1877,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1878,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1879,"question":"songs/08 Sea Of Time_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Time","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1880,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1881,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1882,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1883,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1884,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1885,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1886,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1887,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1888,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1889,"question":"songs/09 Sea Of Holes_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Holes","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1890,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1891,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1892,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1893,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1894,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1895,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1896,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1897,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1898,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1899,"question":"songs/10 Sea Of Monsters_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"Sea Of Monsters","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1900,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1901,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1902,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1903,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1904,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1905,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1906,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1907,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1908,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1909,"question":"songs/11 March Of The Meanies_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"March Of The Meanies","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1910,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1911,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1912,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1913,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1914,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1915,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1916,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1917,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1918,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1919,"question":"songs/12 Pepperland Laid Waste_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"Pepperland Laid Waste","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1920,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_1.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1921,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_2.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1922,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_3.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1923,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_4.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1924,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_5.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1925,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_6.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1926,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_7.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1927,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_8.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1928,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_9.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1929,"question":"songs/13 Yellow Submarine In Pepperland_Yellow Submarine_10.mp3","answer":"Yellow Submarine In Pepperland","categories":["Yellow Submarine"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1930,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1931,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1932,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1933,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1934,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1935,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1936,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1937,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1938,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1939,"question":"songs/01 Love Me Do_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"Love Me Do","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1940,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1941,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1942,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1943,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1944,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1945,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1946,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1947,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1948,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1949,"question":"songs/02 From Me To You_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"From Me To You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1950,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1951,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1952,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1953,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1954,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1955,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1956,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1957,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1958,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1959,"question":"songs/03 Thank You Girl_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"Thank You Girl","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1960,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1961,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1962,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1963,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1964,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1965,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1966,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1967,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1968,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1969,"question":"songs/04 She Loves You_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"She Loves You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1970,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1971,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1972,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1973,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1974,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1975,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1976,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1977,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1978,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1979,"question":"songs/05 I'll Get You_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"I'll Get You","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1980,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1981,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1982,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1983,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1984,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1985,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1986,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1987,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1988,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1989,"question":"songs/06 I Want To Hold Your Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"I Want To Hold Your Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1990,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1991,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1992,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1993,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1994,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1995,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1996,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1997,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1998,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":1999,"question":"songs/07 This Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"This Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2000,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2001,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2002,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2003,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2004,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2005,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2006,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2007,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2008,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2009,"question":"songs/08 Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"Komm, Gib Mir Deine Hand","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2010,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2011,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2012,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2013,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2014,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2015,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2016,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2017,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2018,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2019,"question":"songs/09 Sie Liebt Dich_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"Sie Liebt Dich","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2020,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2021,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2022,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2023,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2024,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2025,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2026,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2027,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2028,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2029,"question":"songs/10 Long Tall Sally_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"Long Tall Sally","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2030,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2031,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2032,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2033,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2034,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2035,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2036,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2037,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2038,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2039,"question":"songs/11 I Call Your Name_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"I Call Your Name","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2040,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2041,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2042,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2043,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2044,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2045,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2046,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2047,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2048,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2049,"question":"songs/12 Slow Down_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"Slow Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2050,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2051,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2052,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2053,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2054,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2055,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2056,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2057,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2058,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2059,"question":"songs/13 Matchbox_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"Matchbox","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2060,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2061,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2062,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2063,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2064,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2065,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2066,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2067,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2068,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2069,"question":"songs/14 I Feel Fine_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"I Feel Fine","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2070,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2071,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2072,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2073,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2074,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2075,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2076,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2077,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2078,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2079,"question":"songs/15 She's A Woman_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"She's A Woman","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2080,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2081,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2082,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2083,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2084,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2085,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2086,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2087,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2088,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2089,"question":"songs/16 Bad Boy_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"Bad Boy","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2090,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2091,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2092,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2093,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2094,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2095,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2096,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2097,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2098,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2099,"question":"songs/17 Yes It Is_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"Yes It Is","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2100,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_1.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2101,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_2.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2102,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_3.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2103,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_4.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2104,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_5.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2105,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_6.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2106,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_7.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2107,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_8.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2108,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_9.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2109,"question":"songs/18 I'm Down_Past Masters, Volume One_10.mp3","answer":"I'm Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume One"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2110,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2111,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2112,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2113,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2114,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2115,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2116,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2117,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2118,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2119,"question":"songs/01 Day Tripper_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Day Tripper","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2120,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2121,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2122,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2123,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2124,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2125,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2126,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2127,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2128,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2129,"question":"songs/02 We Can Work It Out_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"We Can Work It Out","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2130,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2131,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2132,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2133,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2134,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2135,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2136,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2137,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2138,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2139,"question":"songs/03 Paperback Writer_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Paperback Writer","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2140,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2141,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2142,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2143,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2144,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2145,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2146,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2147,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2148,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2149,"question":"songs/04 Rain_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Rain","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2150,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2151,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2152,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2153,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2154,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2155,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2156,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2157,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2158,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2159,"question":"songs/05 Lady Madonna_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Lady Madonna","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2160,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2161,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2162,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2163,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2164,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2165,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2166,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2167,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2168,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2169,"question":"songs/06 The Inner Light_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"The Inner Light","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2170,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2171,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2172,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2173,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2174,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2175,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2176,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2177,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2178,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2179,"question":"songs/07 Hey Jude_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Hey Jude","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2180,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2181,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2182,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2183,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2184,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2185,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2186,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2187,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2188,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2189,"question":"songs/08 Revolution_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Revolution","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2190,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2191,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2192,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2193,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2194,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2195,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2196,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2197,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2198,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2199,"question":"songs/09 Get Back_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Get Back","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2200,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2201,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2202,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2203,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2204,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2205,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2206,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2207,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2208,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2209,"question":"songs/10 Don't Let Me Down_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Don't Let Me Down","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2210,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2211,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2212,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2213,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2214,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2215,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2216,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2217,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2218,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2219,"question":"songs/11 The Ballad Of John And Yoko_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"The Ballad Of John And Yoko","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2220,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2221,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2222,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2223,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2224,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2225,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2226,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2227,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2228,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2229,"question":"songs/12 Old Brown Shoe_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Old Brown Shoe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2230,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2231,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2232,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2233,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2234,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2235,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2236,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2237,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2238,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2239,"question":"songs/13 Across The Universe_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Across The Universe","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2240,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2241,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2242,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2243,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2244,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2245,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2246,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2247,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2248,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2249,"question":"songs/14 Let It Be_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"Let It Be","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2250,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_1.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2251,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_2.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2252,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_3.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2253,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_4.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2254,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_5.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2255,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_6.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2256,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_7.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2257,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_8.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2258,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_9.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true},{"id":2259,"question":"songs/15 You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)_Past Masters, Volume Two_10.mp3","answer":"You Know My Name (Look Up The Number)","categories":["Past Masters, Volume Two"],"selfSufficient":true}]

type QuestionType = {
  id: number
  question: string
  answer: string
  categories: string[]
  selfSufficient: boolean
}

type ConfigType = {
  timePerQuestion: number
  amountOfPossibleVariations: number
  amountOfSuggestions: number
  listOfCategories: string
}

function App() {
  // mantém um valor enquanto as dependências não são modificadas
  const shuffleDataset = useRef(0)

  const dataset = useMemo(() => {
    return fisherYates(ds)
  }, [shuffleDataset])

  const allPossibleAnswers = useMemo(() => {
    return getListFromObjectsAttr(dataset, 'answer')
  }, [])

  const [questions, setQuestions] = useState(fisherYates(dataset))
  const [result, setResult] = useState(false)
  const [wasGivenAnswer, setWasGivenAnswer] = useState(false)
  const [answer, setAnswer] = useState('')
  const [timerKey, setTimerKey] = useState(0)
  const [isInitialConfigOpened, setIsInitialConfigOpened] = useState(true)
  const [questionDate, setQuestionDate] = useState(new Date())
  const [currentConfig, setCurrentConfig] = useState({
    timePerQuestion: 30,
    amountOfPossibleVariations: 2,
    amountOfSuggestions: 3,
    listOfCategories: "A Hard Day's Night; Abbey Road; Beatles For Sale; Help!; Let It Be; Magical Mystery Tour; Please Please Me; Revolver; Rubber Soul; Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band; The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 1]; The Beatles (White Album) [Disc 2]; With The Beatles; Yellow Submarine; Past Masters, Volume One; Past Masters, Volume Two"
  })
  const askedQuestions = useRef<string[]>([])
  const currentQuestion = useRef<QuestionType>()
  const [playedMatches, setPlayedMatches] = useState(0)
  const [points, setPoints] = useState(0)
  const [performance, setPerformance] = useState(0)
  const [record, setRecord] = useState(0)

  const usedTips = useRef(0)

  const totalOfSelfSufficients = useMemo(() => {
    let total = 0
    let splittedListOfCategories = currentConfig.listOfCategories.split(';')
    for (let i = 0; i < dataset.length; i++) {
      if (dataset[i].selfSufficient && atLeastOneInList(dataset[i].categories, splittedListOfCategories))
        total++
    }
    return total
  }, [currentConfig])

  useEffect(() => {
    let storedRecord = localStorage.getItem('record')
    if (!storedRecord) {
      setRecord(0)
    } else {
      setRecord(JSON.parse(storedRecord))
    }

    // let storedConfig = localStorage.getItem('config')
    // if (storedConfig) {
    //   setCurrentConfig(JSON.parse(storedConfig))
    // }
  }, [])

  useEffect(() => {
    if (points > record) {
      localStorage.setItem('record', points.toString())
      setRecord(points)
    }
  }, [points])

  const handleResetTime = () => {
    setTimerKey(timerKey + 1)
  }

  const handleMessageGivenResult = () => {
    if (!wasGivenAnswer) return

    if (result) {
      return 'You are correct!'
    } else {
      return `Oops! The answer was "${currentQuestion.current!.answer}"!`
    }
  }

  const calculatePerformance = (): number => {
    if (playedMatches === 0) return 0

    return Math.round((points / (playedMatches * 10)) * 100)
  }

  const handleNext = () => {
    if (wasGivenAnswer) {
      usedTips.current = 0
      setWasGivenAnswer(false)
      handleResetTime()
      setAnswer('')
      setQuestionDate(new Date())
      setPerformance(calculatePerformance())
    }
  }

  const handleUserAnswer = (answer: string) => {
    if (!currentQuestion.current) return

    setPlayedMatches(currentPlayedMatches => {
      return playedMatches + 1
    })

    askedQuestions.current.push(currentQuestion.current.question)

    setWasGivenAnswer(true)
    if (normalizeString(answer) === normalizeString(currentQuestion.current.answer)) {
      soundEffect('right')
      setResult(true)
      setPoints(currentPoints => {
        return currentPoints + 10 - usedTips.current
      })
    } else {
      soundEffect('wrong')
      setResult(false)
    }
  }

  const defineListOfQuestions = (): QuestionType[] => {
    let end = false, splittedListOfCategories = currentConfig.listOfCategories.split(';')
    let randomQuestion: QuestionType = questions[0]

    if (askedQuestions.current.length >= totalOfSelfSufficients)
      askedQuestions.current = []

    while(!end) {
      randomQuestion = randomFromList(questions)
      if (randomQuestion.selfSufficient && atLeastOneInList(randomQuestion.categories, splittedListOfCategories) && !inList(randomQuestion.question, askedQuestions.current))
        end = true
    }

    currentQuestion.current = randomQuestion

    let finalResult = []
    finalResult.push(randomQuestion)

    let inserted = 0
    for (let i = 0; i < dataset.length; i++) {
      if (randomQuestion.answer === dataset[i].answer && atLeastOneInList(dataset[i].categories, splittedListOfCategories) && dataset[i].id !== randomQuestion.id) {
        finalResult.push(dataset[i])
        inserted++
      }

      if (inserted >= currentConfig.amountOfPossibleVariations)
        break;
    }

    return finalResult
  }

  const handlePlay = (config: ConfigType) => {
    setCurrentConfig(config)
    // localStorage.setItem('config', JSON.stringify(config))
    setIsInitialConfigOpened(false)
    setQuestionDate(new Date())
  }
  
  const updateConfig = (changes: any) => {
    setCurrentConfig(prevCurrentConfig => ({ ...prevCurrentConfig, ...changes }))
  }

  return (
    <div className="container">
      {
        isInitialConfigOpened &&
        <InitialConfig
          onPlay={handlePlay}
          config={currentConfig}
          updateConfig={updateConfig}
        />
      }
      {
        !isInitialConfigOpened &&
        <>
          <Menu
            handleNext={handleNext}
            setIsInitialConfigOpened={setIsInitialConfigOpened}
            points={points}
            performance={performance}
            playedMatches={playedMatches}
            record={record}
          />

          {wasGivenAnswer &&
            <div className="resultMessage">
              {handleMessageGivenResult()}
            </div>
          }


          {!wasGivenAnswer &&
            <>
              <Timer
                initialDate={questionDate}
                limit={currentConfig.timePerQuestion}
                onTimeout={handleUserAnswer}
              />
              <Question
                defineListOfQuestions={defineListOfQuestions}
                usedTips={usedTips}
              />
              <UserInputs
                allPossibleAnswers={allPossibleAnswers}
                amountOfSuggestions={currentConfig.amountOfSuggestions}
                onAnswerSend={handleUserAnswer}
              />
            </>
          }
        </>
      }


    </div>
  )
}

type UserInputsProps = {
  allPossibleAnswers: string[]
  amountOfSuggestions: number,
  onAnswerSend: (answer: string) => void
}

function UserInputs({allPossibleAnswers, amountOfSuggestions, onAnswerSend}: UserInputsProps) {
  const [answer, setAnswer] = useState('')
  const suggestionsVisibility = useRef('none')

  const createSuggestions = () => {
    let suggestions = []
    let ignore = []

    for (let i = 0; i < amountOfSuggestions; i++) {
      // *ordenar as distâncias
      const currentSuggestion = closestElement(answer, allPossibleAnswers, ignore)
      suggestions.push(currentSuggestion)
      ignore.push(currentSuggestion)
    }

    suggestionsVisibility.current = 'flex'

    return suggestions
  } 

  const handleAnswerChange = (e: any) => {
    setAnswer(e.target.value)
  }

  const handleSuggestionSelect = (suggestion: string) => {
    setAnswer(suggestion)
  }

  const handleAnswerSend = () => {
    onAnswerSend(answer)
  }

  return (
    <>
      <div className="suggestions" style={{display: suggestionsVisibility.current}}>
        <Suggestions
          listOfSuggestions={createSuggestions()}
          onSuggestionSelect={handleSuggestionSelect} 
        />
      </div>
      <Answer
        onSend={handleAnswerSend}
        onChange={handleAnswerChange}
        answer={answer}
      />
    </>
  )
}

type InitialConfigProps = {
  onPlay: (config: ConfigType) => void
  updateConfig: (changes: any) => void
  config: ConfigType
}

function InitialConfig({onPlay, updateConfig, config}: InitialConfigProps) {
  return (
    <div className="initialConfig">
      <h1>Beatles Quiz</h1>
      <h2>Configuration</h2>
      <label htmlFor="timePerQuestion">Time per question (in seconds): </label>
      <input onChange={(e) => updateConfig({timePerQuestion: e.target.value})} type="number" id="timePerQuestion" defaultValue={config.timePerQuestion}/>
      <label htmlFor="amountOfPossibleVariations">Amount of possible variations: </label>
      <input onChange={(e) => updateConfig({amountOfPossibleVariations: e.target.value})} type="number" id="amountOfPossibleVariations" defaultValue={config.amountOfPossibleVariations}/>
      <label htmlFor="amountOfSuggestions">Amount of suggestions:</label>
      <input onChange={(e) => updateConfig({amountOfSuggestions: e.target.value})} type="number" id="amountOfSuggestions" defaultValue={config.amountOfSuggestions}/>
      <label htmlFor="includedCategories">Included categories: </label>
      <textarea onChange={(e) => updateConfig({listOfCategories: e.target.value})} style={{height: "100px"}} spellCheck="false" id="includedCategories" defaultValue={config.listOfCategories}></textarea>  

      <button onClick={ () => onPlay(config) }>Play</button>
    </div>
  )
}

type MenuProps = {
  handleNext: () => void
  setIsInitialConfigOpened: (isInitialConfigOpened: boolean) => void
  playedMatches: number
  points: number
  performance: number
  record: number
}

function Menu({handleNext, setIsInitialConfigOpened, playedMatches, points, performance, record}: MenuProps) {
  return (
    <div className="menu">
      <button onClick={ () => { setIsInitialConfigOpened(true) }}><i className="bi bi-gear"></i></button>
      <button>{playedMatches} <i className="bi bi-check-all"></i></button>
      <button>{points} <i className="bi bi-star"></i></button>
      <button>{performance} <i className="bi bi-percent"></i></button>
      <button>{record} <i className="bi bi-award"></i></button>
      <button onClick={ handleNext }><i className="bi bi-arrow-right"></i></button>
    </div>
  )
}

function Slider({elements, usedTips}: any) {
  const [activeElement, setActiveElement] = useState(0)
  const [activeBulletPoint, setActiveBulletPoint] = useState(0)

  const getActiveElement = () => {
    return elements[activeElement]
  }

  const updateActiveElement = (e: any) => {
    usedTips.current++
    let newIndex = parseInt(e.target.getAttribute('id'))
    setActiveElement(newIndex)
    setActiveBulletPoint(newIndex)
  }

  const getControls = () => {
    return elements.map((element: any, index: number) => {
      if (index === activeBulletPoint) {
        return <div key={index} id={index.toString()} onClick={updateActiveElement} style={{width: '1rem', height: '1rem', borderRadius: '50%', backgroundColor: '#fff', cursor: 'pointer', marginRight: '1rem'}}></div>
      } else {
        return <div key={index} id={index.toString()} onClick={updateActiveElement} style={{width: '1rem', height: '1rem', borderRadius: '50%', backgroundColor: '#555', cursor: 'pointer', marginRight: '1rem'}}></div>       
      }
    })
  }

  return (
    <div className="question">
      {getActiveElement()}
      <div className="controls" style={{display: 'flex', justifyContent: 'center', alignItems: 'center', marginTop: '2rem'}}>
        {elements.length > 1 ? getControls() : ''}
      </div>
    </div>
  )
}

type QuestionProps = {
  defineListOfQuestions: () => QuestionType[]
  usedTips: any
}

function Question({ defineListOfQuestions, usedTips }: QuestionProps) {
  const listOfQuestions = defineListOfQuestions()

  if (!listOfQuestions) return <div></div>

  const questionType = (currentQuestion: QuestionType) => {
    if (currentQuestion.question.search('jpg') !== -1 || currentQuestion.question.search('png') !== -1) {
      return <img key={generateUniqueKey()} src={currentQuestion.question}/>
    } else if (currentQuestion.question.search('mp3') !== -1 || currentQuestion.question.search('ogg') !== -1) {
      return (
        <audio key={generateUniqueKey()} controls={true}>
          <source src={currentQuestion.question} type="audio/ogg"/>
          <source src={currentQuestion.question} type="audio/ogg"/>
          Your browser doesn't support the audio tag.
        </audio>
      )
    } else {
      return <div className="textualQuestion" key={generateUniqueKey()}>{currentQuestion.question}</div>
    }
  }

  const createElements = () => {
    return listOfQuestions.map(currentQuestion => {
      return questionType(currentQuestion)
    })
  }

  return (
    <Slider elements={createElements()} usedTips={usedTips}/>
  )
}

type SuggestionsProps = {
  listOfSuggestions: string[]
  onSuggestionSelect: (suggestion: string) => void
}

function Suggestions({listOfSuggestions, onSuggestionSelect}: SuggestionsProps) {
  return (
    <>
    {
      listOfSuggestions.map((suggestion, index) => {
        return <div key={index} onClick={ () => onSuggestionSelect(suggestion)}>{suggestion}</div>
      })
    }
    </>
  )
}

type AnswerProps = {
  onSend: () => void
  onChange: (e: any) => void
  answer: string
}

function Answer({onSend, onChange, answer}: AnswerProps) {
  return (
    <div className="answer">
      <input onChange = {onChange} value={answer} type="text" placeholder="Answer"/>
      <button onClick={ () => onSend() }><i className="bi bi-send"></i></button>
    </div>
  )
}

type TimerProps = {
  initialDate: Date
  limit: number,
  onTimeout: (answer: string) => void
}

function Timer({initialDate, limit, onTimeout}: TimerProps) {
  const [remainingTime, setRemainingTime] = useState(limit)

  useEffect(() => {
    const interval = setInterval(() => {
      let now = new Date()
      let newRemainingTime = Math.ceil(limit - ((now.getTime() - initialDate.getTime()) / 1000))
      if (newRemainingTime <= 0) {
        onTimeout('')
        clearInterval(interval)
      } else {
        setRemainingTime(newRemainingTime)
      }
    }, 100)

    return () => clearInterval(interval)
  }, [initialDate, remainingTime])

  return <div className="timer">{remainingTime} <i className="bi bi-hourglass-split"></i></div>
}

export default App